We decided you should repay with your body.
我们最后还是决定要你用身体来偿还
What?
啥
No, no!
不是不是
I mean we can let him work here to pay off the debt!
我的意思是让他住在这边工作还钱
Did he threaten you, Yuzuki?
妳被这个男人威胁了吗 结月姐
Why would someone like Yuzuki make such a decision?
结月这样的人 怎么会做出这种决定
Did Akagami get something on her?
难道她是被赤神抓住了什么把柄吗
-Do you have any objections? -No.
-妳们没意见吧 -嗯
So, Akagami,
那么赤神
let me show you around this temple.
我来带你参观一下这座寺庙吧
Thank you!
不胜感激
WORLDLY DESIRES
(世俗杂念)
(TenPuru: No One Can Live on Loneliness)
《妙庙美少女》
(Episode 2: Being Lewd Isn't A Bad Thing) This is the main Buddha of our temple.
(第二话 色色不是什么坏事哦) 这个就是本庙的主佛
Wrapped in tape?
竟然还缠着胶带
(Episode 2: Being Lewd Isn't A Bad Thing)
(第二话 色色不是什么坏事哦)
What?
什么
Because we are poor.
因为没钱…
I understand.
我明白了
I will try my best to repay the debt as soon as possible.
我会努力让自己尽快把欠款还清的
With all my might!
倾尽全力
Alright, I'm counting on you.
好的 那就拜托你了
But you can take your time.
不过 你也不要着急 就慢慢来吧
Although I don't know why you want to become a monk,
虽然不知道赤神你为什么想要出家
I can see that you didn't come here
但我能看出来你不是抱着
just to kill time.
随便玩玩的心态过来的
Miss Aoba.
苍叶小姐
Just call me Yuzuki.
你叫我结月就好
After all, there are several Aoba here.
毕竟这里有好几个苍叶呢
Alright.
好的
I'll show you around some other places.
那我再带你去看看别的地方哦
There's definitely something wrong with Yuzuki.
结月姐绝对不太正常
They get along so well.
他们俩的气氛真和谐啊
In this case, we have to do something!
这样一来 我们就必须要做点什么了
Let's kick that guy out
我们得赶快把那个男的赶出去
and make Yuzuki come to her senses!
然后再让结月姐清醒过来！
So, we'll have to seduce him.
那就只有色诱这一招了吧
Kiki, why are you here?
嬉嬉姐 妳怎么会在这
I saw you guys talking about something interesting.
因为月夜妳们 好像在聊很有意思的话题嘛
This is the plan.
具体计划是这样的
First, we seduce Akagami,
我们先诱惑赤神
and once he takes the bait, we'll drive him out.
等他上钩就把他赶出去
That way, Yuzuki will have to accept it.
这样结月也就说不出什么来了吧
I see.
原来如此
So, who's going to seduce Akagami?
那么 要派谁去诱惑赤神呢
That would be
那肯定是
the person with the most desirable figure.
身材最让人垂涎欲滴的人啰
Who are you talking about?
那妳说的是谁…
Me?
我吗
No, no, no.
不不不
Kiki can do it. She's so busty!
让嬉嬉姐去不就好了嘛 她可是个巨乳耶
What are you talking about? I'm a nun.
妳在说什么呢 我可是尼姑哦
Now you remember you're a nun.
妳现在倒想起来自己是尼姑了
Tsukuyo, you can do it.
月夜 加油
Tsukuyo, good luck.
月夜仔 加油
-Wait, hold on. -Tsukuyo, you're so cool when seducing.
-不对 等一下 -月夜姐姐又色又帅
What did you say?
妳说什么
How fulfilling!
好充实
I feel like I'm gradually finding my old self.
我好像开始渐渐找回以前的自己了
That's right, I've found my once pure self.
没错 我找回了那个 曾经纯洁无瑕的自己
Oh, Akagami, you're up so early.
咦 赤神你起的好早哦
Yuzuki.
结月
Good morning.
早哦
Miss Yuzuki, you're up early too.
结月小姐 妳也好早
I have to ring the bell every day
我是因为每天都要去敲钟
to replace my alarm clock at home.
这算是代替我家的闹钟
Alright, see you later.
那我先走啰
Desires!
杂念啊
He was definitely looking at Yuzuki's chest.
他刚刚绝对在看结月姐的胸
I have to find a way to drive this guy out!
我必须想办法把这家伙赶出去
Guys,
大家
breakfast is ready!
早餐已经准备好了
Let me have a taste first.
让我先来小试身手
First, I'll disparage the breakfast he made.
先把这家伙做的早餐贬低得一无是处
I'll dig in.
我开动啦
This is so delicious.
好好吃
What kind of divine taste is this?
这是什么神仙味道
He's a better cook than anyone else here!
比这里所有人做的都好吃
Damn, I want to eat this every day!
失算了 我真想天天都吃这个
I'm so glad it suits your taste.
合妳的口味真是太好了
My work experience when living alone came in handy!
我独立谋生时的打工经验派上用场了
Although I was a little disoriented just now,
虽然刚才我的心思有点被打乱了
there's no need to worry.
不过 我没有必要焦虑
Um, well…
那个 我说…
What…
什么…
He really pays a lot of attention to it.
他真的超级在意呢
This guy definitely has a breast obsession.
这家伙果然是个变态胸奴人啊
I'd like to ask you to do something else.
我想拜托你做下一个工作
Mr. Handyman.
帮手先生
Um…
嗯…
What is this?
这个是…
This is the work uniform, the temple's practice clothing.
这是作务衣 也就是寺庙的修行装
Wear this to work.
你就穿这样工作吧
I lied. It's actually summer clothing.
才怪咧 其实那是夏天才会穿的
The fabric is thin, and he's barefoot.
布料很薄 而且我还让他打赤脚
In November, dressing like that in the temple is unbearable!
在11月的寺庙里 穿成这样无疑就是地狱
-This way, we can get rid of him… -Miss Second!
-这样就能顺利把他… -次女小姐
Thank you very much!
非常感谢
-This is the temple's practice clothing. -What's so happy about?
-这就是寺庙的修行装啊 -这家伙是在高兴什么
Why he called me Miss Second?
还有 他怎么叫我次女小姐啊
Anyway, just get to work.
总之 你先去工作吧
First you'll do the cleaning!
首先是打扫卫生
Yes!
是
I've finished.
我已经打扫完了
No way, it's so clean.
真的耶 这也太干净了
But there are still the bathrooms and toilets.
但你还得去扫浴室 厕所
ANCESTRAL TOMBS And the tombstones.
(历代祖先之墓) 还有墓碑
Of course, I cleaned them all.
我当然都打扫了
This is a day's worth of work!
这是一整天的工作量吧
TEMPLE FINANCIAL SOFTWARE Next is this!
(寺庙会计软件) 那接下来换这个
-If you don't know how to do office work… -This account book…
-如果你不会文职工作的话… -这个账簿
There seems to be a problem.
好像有点问题啊
What? No way!
什么 不会吧
What is the problem?
哪里有问题
-Here. -Ah.
-这里 -啊
Change this part.
将这里像这样改一下
Wow, that's amazing! How did you do it?
哇 好厉害 你是怎么做到的
No!
不对呀
Well then…
既然这样…
Tsukuyo asked me to arrange your practice.
是月夜拜托我给你安排修行的
Sorry, we don't have a waterfall here.
抱歉呀 我们这里没有瀑布
That's alright.
没有关系
This is waterfall practice.
这就是瀑布修行
It's freezing.
可以说是极寒了
Can I endure it?
我能坚持下来吗
If you can't bear it, just say it.
你要是坚持不住了 就快点说出来啊
Stop trying in vain!
不要做无意义的忍耐了
No! I must endure!
不 我一定要坚持下去
I'm back.
我回来了
What are you guys doing?
你们这是在干什么啊
Miss Yuzuki
结月小姐…
in school uniform!
穿制服的模样
How come I feel hot!
怎么回事 我的身体又开始回温了
The hardships just now seemed like nothing.
刚刚的艰辛彷佛不值一提
Could this be enlightenment?
难道这就是…
Great! I did it!
太好了 我做到了
Akagami, what's wrong?
赤神 你怎么了
Go take a bath and warm up!
总之 你先去泡个澡暖暖身体吧
Thank you very much.
真是太感谢妳了
What should I do?
-终于办到了 -怎么办
So we'll have to do it that way, Tsukuyo.
我们果然还是只能那样做了 月夜
Today is a perfect day.
今天真是完美的一天啊
The work and enlightenment went very smoothly.
工作和开悟都非常顺利
Did I slightly repay
结月小姐对我的善意
Miss Yuzuki's kindness?
我是不是多少回报了一些呢
I can't bathe any longer.
不能再泡下去了
I have to go prepare dinner.
我得开始准备餐点才行
This is really rude!
这实在是太失礼了
I'm sorry. What's the matter?
对不起 这到底是怎么了
Why is she taking off her clothes?
她为什么要脱衣服
I have to stay calm.
我要冷静
Let me sort out my thoughts.
先整理一下目前的状况 赤神明光
No. I can't understand it at all!
不行 我完全搞不懂
What on earth is happening?
这到底是怎么回事啊
I took off my clothes too early.
我太早脱衣服了
Am I an idiot?
我该不会是个傻瓜吧
I suddenly took off my clothes. I'm nothing but a female delinquent!
突然就把衣服脱掉 我简直就是个女色情狂嘛
I was supposed to take off my clothes in a panic,
我本来应该是要趁乱脱掉衣服
and then be discovered by Yuzuki.
再被路过的结月姐给发现的
But after seeing his naked body, my mind went blank.
结果 我看到那家伙的裸体后
Anyway,
总之
I have to find a way to turn the tables.
我得想办法逆转局面
YUZUKI WILL GO TO THE BATHROOM IN FIVE MINUTES Before Yuzuki comes,
(结月姐 五分钟之后来浴室一下) 在结月姐过来之前
I must create a scene of being attacked by Akagami.
我必须要搞出被赤神袭击的场景来
If I take off a little more now,
事已至此 我只要再稍微脱掉一点
he should pounce on me.
那家伙应该就会扑上来了
No, this is my limit.
不行不行 我已经到极限了
If I continue to take off, I'll be naked! Now I'm really a female delinquent!
再脱下去我就要被看光了 那我就真的变成女色情狂了
I…
那…那个…
Watch out!
小心
Miss Second, are you alright?
次女小姐 妳没事…
Tsukuyo, what happened? What was that loud noise?
月夜 怎么了 搞出那么大声音来…
No! This is…
那 那个 这个是 呃呃啊
I didn't mean to go this far.
我本来没有要做到这种地步的
Eh? Why am I the one trying to explain?
咦 我为什么在找借口解释啊
Anyway, the plan was successful.
总之计划应该算是成功了
Akagami.
赤神
Yes.
啊 我在
Please leave for now.
请你先从这里出去吧
Eh?
咦
I'm so touched!
我好感动
Tsukuyo stepped forward
月夜妳竟然挺身而出
and made the seduction plan a success!
让色诱计划成功了
As expected of Tsukuyo.
真不愧是月夜仔
Sis Tsukuyo is so lewd and cool.
月夜姐姐又色情狂又帅
Kurage, ever since yesterday, you've been talking about me strangely.
海月 妳从昨天开始 对我的评价就很奇怪
What did you actually do?
妳到底使出了怎样的绝招
Can you tell us?
可以跟我们说说吗
Now we can kick that guy out completely!
这样一来 把那个男人赶出去的计划 就彻底完成了
Kick him out?
赶出去…吗
But why am I so restless?
可是我为什么会感到闷闷不乐啊
Sis Yuzuki.
结月姐
Huh?
咦
Hey, Yuzuki.
喂 结月姐
Yuzuki.
结月姐
No, this is so weird.
不对不对 好奇怪
I can understand if she's avoiding Akagami.
她要是躲开赤神我倒是可以理解
But why is she avoiding me too.
但她为什么要躲我
Yuzuki!
结月姐
Why are you avoiding me?
妳为什么要躲着我呀
Wait! Don't come over, Tsukuyo.
等等 妳别过来 月夜
What are you saying? You're going too far.
妳是怎样啦 也太过分了吧
I feel a bit embarrassed too,
虽然我也会感到有点尴尬
but you are ignoring me.
但是妳无视我…
Yuzuki?
结月姐
It's not like that! Whenever I see your face, I can't help but think of…
不是这样的 一看见月夜的脸 我就会忍不住想起来…
Think of what?
想起来…想起来什么
Akagami's naked body.
赤神的裸体
Actually, just a small part of his body.
与其说是裸体… 倒不如说是他身体的一小部分
Yuzuki, you're so lewd.
结月姐 妳好下流
Lewd!
下流
You are the lewd one, Tsukuyo!
下流的是月夜吧
Talking about a seduction plan.
还说什么色诱计划
Eh, how did you know?
咦 妳怎么会知道
Kiki told me.
是嬉嬉姐告诉我的
That nun!
那个尼姑啊啊啊
Yuzuki,
我说结月姐
why did you agree to let Akagami live in our temple?
妳为什么会同意 让赤神住进我们寺庙呢
You still don't accept him?
妳果然还是不愿意吗
It's more like I find it strange
与其说是不愿意 不如说是觉得很奇怪
that a male attendant is in a nunnery.
尼姑庵里居然有男寺务员
I didn't accept it without hesitation.
虽然我也还没完全接受这件事…
But I think mother would definitely do so.
但我认为如果是妈妈 她肯定会这么做的吧
-She would. -Right?
-确实 -对吧
She would definitely welcome anyone who wants to live in this temple.
她肯定会说 想住进这个寺庙的人就尽管来好了
Yeah, she would welcome anyone.
啊 真像她会说的话 而且还是不论男女
Besides,
还有
Akagami seemed very unwilling.
赤神看起来也很不甘心
He really wanted to change himself.
他是真的想改变自己
Unwillingness is the proof of sincerity.
不甘心就是真心的证明
Although I can only see a little bit,
虽然我只能看出来一点点
Akagami is easy to understand.
但是赤神很好懂的
Have I ever tried to get to know that guy?
我有没有…好好了解过那家伙呢
I lost to you, Yuzuki.
我果然还是敌不过结月姐呢
Back then,
回想起来…
He protected me too.
那家伙也在那时候保护我了呢
So, Tsukuyo.
那么月夜
Let's go find Akagami and explain it.
我们去找赤神把事情解释清楚吧
Akagami
赤神那家伙
just packed his luggage and left.
刚才已经收拾行李走掉了哦
Eh?
啊
PRETTY GIRLS OF THE TEMPLE HARMED THEMSELVES WHEN HARMING OTHERS.
(妙庙美少女 害人终害己)
I can't
我已经
face them anymore.
没脸再见她们了
Akagami.
赤神
Please leave for now.
请你先从这里出去吧
I can't keep embarrassing myself.
我不能再继续丢人现眼了
TEMPLE POLICE STATION I might as well turn myself in!
(寺庙派出所) 我还是去自首吧！
WANTED CRIMINAL Yes, not long ago,
(重要通缉犯) 我是因为刚才
a female roommate peeked at me while I was taking a bath.
被同居的女性偷看我洗澡
For some reason, she suddenly started undressing.
然后不知为何她突然开始脱衣服
And I stole a kiss from her.
我又因为一个闪失而夺走了她的吻
So, I'm turning myself in.
所以才来自首的
Don't come back.
你不要再来了
Why?
为什么
Maybe I should go back to my old house.
没办法 我还是先回之前住的房子吧
A new tenant moved in.
咦 新住户已经住进去了哦
So what about my belongings?
那…那我的东西呢
We threw them away.
我都扔掉了
I'm homeless now.
我居然无家可归了
Is everyone eating well?
大家有没有好好吃饭啊
With Miss Yuzuki around, there's definitely no problem.
不 有结月小姐在的话 肯定是没问题的
She might seem like an innocent young lady at first glance,
虽然她乍看之下 是个不谙世事的千金大小姐
but she's actually a very reliable woman.
但她实际上是个值得依靠的女性
She also got up very early today.
今天她也是很早就起床了
Desires.
杂念啊
Wait, no way.
等等 不会吧
I've already attained enlightenment, but I still have desires.
我如今已经开悟 竟然还会有杂念
That's right, my enlightenment
没错 我的开悟
was achieved through the help of Miss Second.
是在次女小姐的帮助下修行得来的
She is beautiful and competitive.
她既美丽又好胜
She seems to have quite a lot of interactions with boys.
与异性的交流好像也蛮广泛的
But she must have been deeply affected.
虽说如此 但她肯定深受打击了吧
Why am I still plagued with desires?
我为什么还是杂念缠身呢
Didn't I attain enlightenment after my waterfall practice?
我经过瀑布修行之后不是开悟了吗
In that case,
既然如此
even if I can only repay my debts,
就算只能还清欠款
ORGAN SELLING. SAY GOODBYE TO DEBT, WE WILL BUY YOUR PRECIOUS PROPERTY AT A HIGH PRICE. I will put my life on the line.
(出售器官告别欠款 高价收购您宝贵的财产) 我也要拼上这条命
AKAGAMI OWES 20 MILLION YEN. ESTIMATED VALUE FOR AKAGAMI'S ORGANS IS 18.9 MILLION YEN.
(赤神欠款2000万元 赤神内脏售价预估1890万元)
In the end,
难道…
I can't do anything on my own.
我一个人的话 终究还是什么都做不到吗
What are you doing?
你在做什么啊
It's winter now!
现在可是冬天啊
You could die!
这样会死人的
Akagami! Look at me.
赤神 你好好看着我
Why do you always avoid looking at me?
你为什么不敢看我
Because I can't bear to look directly at you.
因为妳现在简直不忍直视啊
Geez!
真是的
How could you just run out of the temple like that?
你怎么突然就从寺庙里跑出去了呢
Because you told me to leave.
那是因为结月小姐 妳让我出去 所以我才…
Bathroom!
浴室
I meant for you to leave the bathroom!
我的意思是让你从浴室出去
Bathroom?
浴室吗
Listen, Akagami!
听好了 赤神
You're still a child.
你还是个小孩子
You should act more spoiled!
你应该多依赖一下周遭的人
As for what happened in the bathroom,
浴室里发生的事情
you just need to explain yourself and it'll be fine!
你只要把事情经过说清楚就没关系了
Please rely on me more.
请再多依靠我一些吧
Akagami, you're a newcomer and a child.
赤神 你既是新人又是小孩子
How old are you, Akagami?
赤神你今年多大
I'm 21.
我21岁了
ORANGE You're the older one.
原来你年纪比我大啊
Aoba Yuzuki. I am 17.
我是苍叶结月 今年17岁
ORANGE Glad to know.
妳客气了
You're a mature adult now.
既然你都是个成熟的大人了
You should act more spoiled!
那就给我好好依赖周遭的人啊
If you don't know how to act spoiled
如果你不知道要怎么依赖
or how to ask for help,
还有要怎么拜托别人的话
you can rely on me
这所有一切
for all of that!
你都只要依赖我就好了
Miss Yuzuki.
结月小姐…
Although I only had a vague feeling before,
虽然我之前已经隐隐察觉到了
now I see that she truly is very passionate.
但是她的头脑也太单纯了吧
-Akagami! -Yes.
-赤神 -我在
The first lesson you have learned is
这是我最初开悟的心得 其一
that people cannot survive alone!
人是无法一个人生存下去的
Since you've come to our temple,
既然你来到了我们寺庙
we won't let you be alone anymore.
我就不会再让你一个人了
-Tsukuyo, what do you think? -Eh?
-月夜 妳是怎么想的 -咦
Miss Second.
次女小姐…
I'm sorry!
抱歉
ORANGE I shouldn't have set you up. I'm sorry.
我不应该设计陷害你 对不起
I shouldn't have assumed that you were insincere. I'm sorry.
也不应该认定你不真诚 对不起
No, I also looked at your chest.
不 我也要对看过以及摸过
I even touched it and pushed you down.
妳胸部 甚至还推倒妳…
Stop talking, you idiot!
别再说了 你这个笨蛋
Alright! I'm sorry!
好 对不起
Let's go back, Akagami!
回去吧 赤神
-I'm hungry! -I understand!
-我饿了 -我明白了
So, Akagami, hold out your hand!
那么赤神 你把手伸出来
FIRST KISS FEE: 5 MILLION YEN, AOBA TSUKUYO That was my first kiss.
(接吻费500万日元 苍叶月夜) 那是我的初吻
So, you'll take responsibility, right?
你要负起责任喔
So realistic.
这也太现实啦
I'm back.
我回来啦
Welcome back.
欢迎回来
I'm back too!
我也回来了
Please allow me
请允许我
to return to this temple!
再次回到这个寺庙
Shut up and just get in.
别说了 你快点进去啦
Tsukuyo.
月…月夜
Why is this guy back?
为什么这个男人又回来了
It's okay to just let him stay.
啊 因为我想说让他住一下 应该也没关系吧
Thank you very much!
非常感谢
Mia!
米亚
What's going on with her?
她这是…
It is a bit complicated.
情况有些复杂
Tsukuyo, do you want to
月夜 妳要不要
take a bath with me?
和我一起泡澡
That's right.
她说的对
Miss Second, you're also soaked from the rain.
次女小姐妳的衣服也被雨淋透了
I'M NOT I'll pass.
(才没有) 我就不用了
By the way,
话说
just call me Tsukuyo.
你叫我月夜就行了
It's a bit embarrassing.
不然我怪难为情的
Alright, got it.
嗯 好的
Welcome back, Sis Tsukuyo.
欢迎回来 月夜姐姐
Kurage.
海月
Akagami, you're back too.
赤神哥哥 你也回来了啊
Yes, Miss Third.
是的 三女小姐
I'm really ashamed.
真是说来惭愧
Kurage is Miss Third, right?
原来你叫海月三女小姐啊
Yuzuki said she's waiting for you in the bathroom.
结月姐姐说她在浴室等着妳哦
There's no need to rush, right?
不用那么着急吧
The usually reliable Yuzuki
平时挺可靠的结月姐
is acting quite carelessly today.
今天却一反常态地那么冒失
She used to be even more silly.
她以前要更笨一些呢
She was carefree and straightforward.
随心所欲又言行耿直
-Seemed thoughtful but actually empty-headed. -Stop it, Kurage.
-看起来深思熟虑实则脑袋空空 -别说了 海月
It's true that she was even more careless before though.
虽然以前的结月姐 确实要比现在更脱线一点
Useless?
没用的人
What?
妳说没用的人吗
Alright, you successfully confused me.
好吧 妳成功把姐姐我绕晕了
No, Miss Third.
不可以 三女小姐
You can't speak ill of your sister.
妳不可以说妳姐姐的坏话
That's right.
没错没错
Yuzuki is just a bit too thoughtless.
结月只是神经过于大条而已
You're not making it sound better.
你说的也没好到哪里去
Tsukuyo, hurry up!
月夜 妳快点啦
I got it, Yuzuki.
我知道啦 结月姐
I feel a bit off lately.
我最近总感觉自己不在状态
Tsukuyo loves our big sister too.
月夜姐姐也有点姐控
Uh, it's already this late.
哎呀 都这个时间了
Miss Third, I'm going to prepare dinner.
三女小姐 我要准备做晚餐了
I'll help you.
我帮你
Speaking of which,
话说回来
you said Miss Yuzuki is useless.
刚刚妳说结月小姐很没用…
It's true.
那是真的
It's hard to imagine.
我实在是难以想象啊
Of course, you've only just met her.
那当然 毕竟你们才认识没多久
That's true.
那倒也是
But I really want to know!
但是 我超想知道的
Don't be silly!
别蠢了
It's an invasion of privacy.
这可是侵犯他人隐私
But,
但是
the 17 years of Miss Yuzuki's life that I don't know,
我不了解的17年间的结月小姐
I want to know everything if possible!
可以的话 我现在就想知道 她所有的一切
Do you want to peep into the bathroom?
你想偷窥她们洗澡吗
Why do you ask that?
妳为什么突然这么问
You just said you want to know everything.
因为你刚刚说你想知道她所有的一切
Did I accidentally say it out loud?
我不小心说出声了吗
No, I definitely didn't mean it.
不 我绝没有那种非分之想
Besides, this is a temple.
更何况这里还是寺庙
Shamelessness is like a capital crime.
心怀不轨可是相当于死罪
Being lewd is not a bad thing.
色色不是什么坏事哦
What?
什…什么
We're all human.
我们都是人嘛
Even Buddha has children.
你想想 佛陀也是有孩子的
I'm also a monk's child.
我也是和尚的孩子
The thing between men and women…
也就是说男女之事…
Stop, Miss Third.
停停停 三女小姐
And Yuzuki is probably quite lewd too.
而且结月姐姐应该也很色哦
In a repressed way.
她是那种闷骚的色哦
Repressed?
闷骚吗
So I think even if you peep, she probably wouldn't get angry.
所以即使你去偷窥她 我想她应该也不会生气的
That's not right.
不对不对 这道理也太奇怪了
This child is so innocent.
这…这孩子 她好纯洁
And that makes her very dangerous.
正因如此 她也十分危险
Well…
那…那个
I was joking.
我开玩笑的
Huh?
啊
Yuzuki used to like
结月姐姐以前很喜欢
teasing others like that.
这样捉弄别人
But since then,
但是从那时起
she became perfect.
结月姐姐就变得很完美了
So did Tsukuyo.
然后月夜姐姐也是
She gradually became more like an adult.
渐渐变得像大人了
But after you came,
但是赤神哥哥你来了之后
they began to look stupid.
她们两个又有点变回笨蛋了
I prefer when they are stupid.
我更喜欢她们两个笨蛋的一面
So, I'm very happy
所以赤神哥哥你能回来
that you came back.
我觉得很开心
Thank you.
谢谢你
She's such a good child.
她真是个好孩子啊
Don't thank me!
不用向我道谢
So, as a reward,
所以作为回报
I'll show you.
我就让你看吧
Eh?
咦
Everything about my sisters.
姐姐们的全部
Stop! Miss Third!
等一下 三女小姐
-Stop! -Done it.
-住手 -我转
Geez. Don't tease Akagami anymore.
真是的…妳不要再捉弄赤神了哦
Okay.
好
I understand, Miss Third.
妳明白了吧 三女小姐
Being lewd is wrong.
色色是不对的
You seem very happy.
你看起来很开心嘛
But,
但是
this temple is depraved!
这个寺庙已经堕落了
Akagami! It's all your fault!
赤神 这都是你的错
NEXT EPISODE Akagami saw
(下集 让我把你阉了吧) 我被赤神看到
(Let Me Castrate You) my private part.
女孩子害羞的地方了
Could it be…
咦 该不会…
He saw me licking the ice cream lid.
他看见我舔冰淇淋的盖子了
Oh my, I thought it was there.
吓我一跳 我还以为是那种地方呢
-By the way, he also saw my chest. -Akagami?
-顺带一提 我还被看到胸部了哦 -赤神啊